

Natasha Hockey

@_tashhockey

PROFILE

22 - year old web design graduate living in the South West with a passion for UX / UI. Currently working as a UX designer at The Idea Bureau.

Organiser of Be Creative, a monthly event that encourages creatives within the industry and students to network.

Time away from the screen is spent going on adventures with a polaroid camera or doing brush lettering. Oh and I'm the biggest lover of dogs.

SKILLS

Sketch - InVision - Zeplin Adobe CC - Typography - User
Experience - User Research Prototyping - Wireframing Writing - GitHub - Design
Thinking - Project Management
- Dropmark - HTML - CSS/SCSS

CONTACT

(+44) 7496512244 natasha.hockey@live.com http://natashahockey.me

EDUCATION

WEB DESIGN & DEVELOPMENT @ SOLENT UNIVERSITY

September 2014 - May 2017

Spent 3 years studying at Southampton Solent University where skills were developed in UX / UI, HTML, CSS, JS, SQL and PHP. Work experience was also gained during this time.

A-LEVELS @ HUISH EPISCOPI ACADEMY

September 2011 - July 2013

Studied ICT, Media and Art & Design where the passion to design websites unfolded. Worked hard in learning the basics of HTML / CSS and best design practices over 2 years.

WORK EXPERIENCE

UX DESIGNER @ THE IDEA BUREAU (TAUNTON, UK) May 2016 -

Joined The Idea Bureau team as a second year student. Working on understanding users and designing interfaces and interactive prototypes for websites / apps. Whilst also helping to build upon the design workflow.

INTERN DESIGNER @ RARELOOP (SOUTHAMPTON, UK)

January 2016 - June 2016

Part-time position helping to research, design and test websites and apps for exciting and challenging client briefs.

STUDENT REPRESENTATIVE @ SOLENT UNIVERSITY

September 2015 - October 2016

Helping to raise awareness and resolve issues for students on the BSc (Hons) Web Design & Development course through regular meetings and discussions.

KEYHOLDER @ MARSTONS (ILMINSTER & SOUTHAMPTON, UK)

October 2011 - September 2015

Worked in a restaurant and bar for 4 years with the responsibility of cash handling, dealing with complaints and managing a team under pressure.